twinriversusd.org 2018-11-25

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Twin River Unified School District strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet
technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally
Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to
the terms of this privacy policy. Please note this policy applies only to information collected by
Twin River Unified School District online and does not impact information collected or used by
Twin River Unified School District or its affiliates through other means.
How we gather information from users.
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in
which you elect to participate and the services provided. You can visit many pages on our site
without providing any information. Other pages may prompt you to provide information, such as
when you register for access to portions of our site, sign up for membership, request certain
features (e.g., newsletters, news updates and other products), sign up for a newspaper
subscription or make a purchase. You may also provide information when you participate in
sweepstakes and contests, voting and polling activities, message boards and chat rooms and other
interactive areas of our site.
Like most Web sites, Twin River Unified School District also collects information automatically
and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we
may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use "cookie" technology. Among other
things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter
that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a
particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also
gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with
information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but doing so may
limit your ability to access certain portions of the site or may require you to re-enter your user
name and password. Additionally we may not be able to customize the site's features according
to your preferences.
A cookie gets entered by your Web browser into the "Cookies" folder on your hard drive after
you close your browser, and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. We
use persistent and session cookies to analyze and enhance your experience on the Site. The data
that is collected is the property of Twin Rivers Unified School District, not the third party.
What we do with the information we collect.
We will use your information only as permitted by law. Aggregated Information (information
that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. As one example, we may
combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other
users to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive. Aggregated
Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners, but cannot be
used to contact you individually.

We also collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and
advertising. For example, we may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on Twin
River Unified School District to communicate with you regarding our Terms of Service and
privacy policy, products and services offered by Twin River Unified School District and other
affiliates and partners, administration of sweepstakes and contests, processing e-commerce
transactions and other topics we think you might find of interest. We reserve the right to share
this information with other business units and affiliates. This policy does not apply to any
Affiliate's use of such information.
Personally Identifiable Information collected by Twin River Unified School District may also be
used for other purposes including but not limited to site administration and troubleshooting.
Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting
service and our newsletter provider, for example) may access such information.
As we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other
companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred
assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when
we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of
amounts you may owe to us, and/or whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary to give such
information to law enforcement authorities. Please note we may not provide you with notice
prior to disclosure in such cases.
Your choice to opt out.
Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. Should you choose to voluntarily
disclose Personally Identifiable Information on our site, such as in message boards, chat areas or
in advertising or notices you post, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected
and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from
other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Twin River Unified
School District and this policy.
Children
Twin River Unified School District does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable
Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have
received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that
information immediately. If you believe Twin River Unified School District has any information
from or about anyone under 13, please contact us.
Changes to this policy.
Twin River Unified School District reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please
check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of
changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the
time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the
information was collected. Governing law.

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by United States law. Any claim related to the
Site or this policy shall be brought in a federal or state court in the United States, within one year
after the claim arises. You agree no such claim may be brought as a class action. Users of Twin
River Unified School District consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such court as the most
convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this policy. Twin River
Unified School District is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United
States. If you are located outside the United States, please note the information you provide to us
will be transferred to the United States. You hereby consent to this transfer.
In the event case of any conflict between the terms of this policy and the terms of any electronic
or machine readable privacy policy (for example, a P3P electronic privacy policy), the terms of
this written policy shall control.
